The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Demon Spirit Land
East Demon Spirit Sea
How can the spiritual energy in here be so thin ?
It’s no different from the mortal world.
I don't know anything about this place
so I should first find someone to question.
Found it.
Thirteen
Luo Family Tribe
I’ve finally got you.
Luo Family Valley
This formation is exceedingly profound.
It can conceal all signs of life.
It was made with a different method than that of the Cultivation Alliance.
It looks like the work of ancient cultivators.
It’s him !
Where are we ?
And what is this formation guarding ?
I won’t tell you.
If you kill me,
Patriarch Ouyang won’t let you go !
I am Wang Lin,
I request to speak with whoever owns this valley.
Ouyang Hua
Luo Family Tribe Leader
Outsider,
return my tribe members
and fuck off my tribe's territory !
Don't come any closer !
What you're looking for
isn't here !
What I'm looking for ?
An avatar ?
Kill !
This formation uses neither spiritual energy
nor celestial spiritual energy
yet it somehow rivals my Ancient God Restrictions...
Interesting.
I thought you had more tricks up your sleeve
but you’re nothing special.
Die !
No matter how different, it's all the same.
No matter how complex a formation is,
it's always nothing more than a type of restriction.
As long as I can understand it,
it can be unraveled.
Impossible !
Celestial,
you're actually breaking the formation !
Spare me, Celestial !
Ouyang Hua
was wrong.
This formation protects the lives of my tribe.
I beg Celestial to understand,
please don't destroy it.
Open the gate.
Celestial,
please.
They don't have a hint of spiritual energy
yet are able to control this huge formation.
It's really weird...
What's the
mystery of this valley ?
Da Bao, Xiao Bao, come home for dinner !
They’re...
all mortals ?
The child meant no offense,
I hope Celestial doesn't mind.
I assumed such a powerful formation had to be guarding something
but it’s just a village of mortals.
This jade bottle contains several dozen pills
to strengthen your foundation.
I'm sorry for bothering you,
I shall take my leave now.
Celestial, please wait !
The Demon Spirit Night is about to begin.
It's already dusk.
If Celestial doesn’t mind,
please stay here for the night.
Demon Spirit Night ?
On every full moon,
all the demon spirits lurking in the Demon Spirit Land
come out to hunt
and kill every living thing in sight.
Over time,
people began calling this night
the Demon Spirit Night.
Legend has it that countless years ago,
a celestial brought our ancestors here to settle
and laid down this formation
to spare us from the scourge of the Demon Spirit Nights.
Patriarch Huanglong ?
How do you know the name of Celestial Huang Long ?
Do you know him ?
No.
The Huanglong I knew was only at Foundation Establishment.
He can't be the same person as this painting.
I have another question.
You said that
this place doesn’t have what I'm looking for.
What is it exactly ?
That item is tied to the life of my tribe.
If you take it by force,
it will hurt our tribe members' foundations
and they may even wither and die.
That's why
I tried to stop you from entering the tribe.
However,
if Celestial still has those pills you gave us earlier
to strengthen our tribe members' foundations,
we would willingly give Celestial what he's looking for.
Is this enough ?
Yes... it's enough !
Thank you, Celestial.
An outsider’s pills
are worth a fortune in the Demon Spirit Land.
Celestial,
please follow me.
I’ll take you to it.
Back mountain
of the Luo Family Tribe
This fluctuation
isn't celestial spiritual energy.
Celestial's eye is keen.
This isn't celestial spiritual energy.
It's the unique demonic energy of the Demon Spirit Land.
Rank 1 Demon Spirit Crystal
What you're looking for
is precisely this Demon Spirit Crystal, condensed from demonic energy.
No wonder he showed no hints of spiritual energy
but was able to operate the formation.
The Demon Spirit Crystal
must be the key in this Demon Spirit Land.
I will cultivate here.
You may leave.
Understood.
We'll make it through the night
and we'll survive !
The demon spirits seem unusually fierce tonight.
If the formation can’t hold,
will...
Will he help us ?
Patriarch !
Why is the demonic energy so strong tonight ?
How can it be this powerful !?
Hold the line !
What do we do ?
Don’t panic !
It’s over !
We’re all doomed !
Celestial !
The Celestial has come !
Return to the valley !
Whoever you are,
show yourself !
Your cultivation isn't bad
to be able to sense my presence.
Luo Yun
Heavenly Ghost Sect
Peak Late stage Soul Transformation
Are you from the Da Lou Sword Sect ?
Out of respect for your sect,
if you hand over your Demon Spirit Crystal,
I’ll spare your life.
That's what you get for refusing my kindness !
Death Finger !
This spell...
It's the same one that I saw at the All-Seer's birthday...
You
are the All-Seer's new disciple !
The Seventh Purple Disciple,
Wang Lin !
This man can fight an Ascendant...
If I knew it was him,
I wouldn't have provoked him.
You can’t escape.
Even if you’re a prodigy,
you’re only at Middle stage Soul Transformation !
You
are pushing your luck !
Forbidden Devil,
Fourth Heavenly Ghost !
You forced me to wound my own Origin Soul
and use a forbidden spell !
You deserve
to die !
A soul ?
It was about time.
This will allow the Soul Lasher to evolve.
The Heavenly Ghost’s soul
will feed the Soul Lasher !
An artifact specialized in damaging souls ?
Welcome back, Celestial !
I’ll borrow your back mountain.
Don't disturb me
unless it’s urgent.
From now on,
the back mountain is a forbidden area.
It's off limits !
This is the tribe's rule.
Those who violate it
will be banished outside
to fend for themselves !
Understood.
Disciples of the Heavenly Ghost Sect are protected by ghost spirits.
If you kill me,
my master, Daoist Ghost, will avenge me !
Even the All-Seer
treats my master as a peer !
Wang Lin,
think carefully !
You dare to Soul Search me !?
My master will never let you go !
The Demon Spirit Land is divided into 9 countries.
Each country is ruled by a Demon Emperor
and has over 100 cities governed by
8 Demon Generals under the Demon Emperor.
These 9 countries
each belong to one of the 9 Ancient Demon Spirits
that live in this place.
Fusing with an Ancient Demon Spirit
is the true goal of us cultivators.
Ancient Demon Spirits are naturally born of heaven and earth.
If a cultivator fuses with one,
not only will their cultivation surge
but they’ll also gain heaven-defying abilities.
Luo Yun’s memories even mention a rumor.
Those who fuse with an Ancient Demon Spirit
have a tiny chance
of entering a state known as the Beginning of the Soul.
Beginning of the Soul ?
Could it be...
the Shi Realm ?
Ji Realm
Shi Realm
Dao Realm
The 3 legendary realms involve spiritual energy and Divine Sense.
If I grasp Death from the Ji Realm
and Life from the Shi Realm,
my Dao of Life and Death
might one day reach a higher state.
It's too early to be thinking about this.
According to Luo Yun,
only with enough demonic energy
and by accumulating military merit
can one earn an audience with the Ancient Demon Spirit.
I'm currently in the Sky Demon Country
and the nearest city is Ancient Demon City.
Luo Yun invaded the valley
for this rank 1 Demon Spirit Crystal
Rank 2 Demon Spirit Crystal
to merge it with his rank 2 crystal
and gain qualifications to enter Ancient Demon City.
Rank 3 Demon Spirit Crystal
Then, as a soldier in the army,
he would join in campaigns
to accumulate merit
and rise through the ranks.
This is the path most cultivators will choose to follow.
But joining the army as a soldier
would leave me at the mercy of others.
In that case,
it might be better to teach the tribe how to make Soul Flags
to build an army of my own.
Quick reminder of the 3 legendary realms of spiritual energy and Divine Sense because it was never really explained in the donghua.
- The Ji Realm, the extreme realm that grants unprecedented power and represents Death.
- The Shi Realm, if Ji is Death then Shi is Life.
- The Dao Realm, the most sought after and the most mysterious.
Wang Lin lacks information at the moment about the Shi and Dao Realms.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?